{
    "subject": "Harry_Enfield",
    "predicate": "produced",
    "object": "Kevin_&_Perry_Go_Large",
    "human_readable": "Harry Enfield produced Kevin & Perry Go Large.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8939840197563171,
            "question": "Who produced the movie Kevin & Perry Go Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8344435691833496,
            "question": "When was Kevin & Perry Go Large released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7305213809013367,
            "question": "What is the genre of Kevin & Perry Go Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6969637274742126,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in Kevin & Perry Go Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6453309655189514,
            "question": "What type of media is Kevin & Perry Go Large?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5781348943710327,
            "question": "What is the name of the film that Harry Enfield produced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.520743727684021,
            "question": "Is Harry Enfield known for producing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4480563998222351,
            "question": "What is Harry Enfield famous for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38845402002334595,
            "question": "Name a movie made by Harry Enfield."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26182401180267334,
            "question": "Has Harry Enfield won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Harry Enfield produced Kevin & Perry Go Large.",
            "html": "yago_21006_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a movie made by Harry Enfield.",
            "html": "yago_21006_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Harry Enfield famous for?",
            "html": "yago_21006_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Harry Enfield known for producing films?",
            "html": "yago_21006_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_21006_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` "
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple, as all four files (3.txt, 48.txt, 69.txt, and 70.txt) mention Harry Enfield's involvement with the film Kevin & Perry Go Large, specifically that he played a starring role, was a writer, or was involved in some other capacity."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the film \"Kevin and Perry Go Large,\" including details on its production, which mentions that it was written by Dave Cummings and Harry Enfield. This supports the statement that Harry Enfield produced Kevin & Perry Go Large, considering he was involved in writing for the film."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}